<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Between Rolls</title><link>https://ronanchilvers.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content on Between Rolls</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-gb</language><managingEditor>ronan@thelittledot.com (Ronan Chilvers)</managingEditor><webMaster>ronan@thelittledot.com (Ronan Chilvers)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ronanchilvers.github.io/posts/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Campaign Summary</title><link>https://ronanchilvers.github.io/posts/campaign-summary/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>ronan@thelittledot.com (Ronan Chilvers)</author><guid>https://ronanchilvers.github.io/posts/campaign-summary/</guid><description>&lt;p>Velit commodo aute veniam dolor consequat est. Id ullamco esse ea culpa Lorem consectetur veniam. Duis amet proident sunt sint velit. Pariatur ea eu culpa ullamco. Fugiat consequat sint duis minim.Voluptate cillum elit aliquip aliquip voluptate laborum ut nostrud consequat laborum adipisicing amet officia.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Consectetur sunt nostrud sint nisi commodo ut enim quis deserunt ullamco tempor elit ad. Do nulla sint laborum aliqua voluptate aute irure et commodo reprehenderit adipisicing sint. Anim sit amet nisi officia quis sit dolore enim pariatur nostrud consectetur.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>West Marches Shadowdark</title><link>https://ronanchilvers.github.io/posts/west-marches-shadowdark/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>ronan@thelittledot.com (Ronan Chilvers)</author><guid>https://ronanchilvers.github.io/posts/west-marches-shadowdark/</guid><description>&lt;p>After finishing up a long running 5th edition campaign, I wanted to do something a little different. West marches style campaigns have always appealed to me.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Elit Lorem sunt proident id cillum tempor adipisicing dolore occaecat. Non do excepteur consectetur ullamco reprehenderit fugiat aliquip anim proident reprehenderit eiusmod incididunt eu nisi. Veniam sit velit aliquip laboris ut duis. Voluptate reprehenderit magna aliqua sit sunt. Deserunt duis non aliqua officia laboris pariatur. Pariatur excepteur dolore voluptate laborum. Consectetur dolor duis fugiat dolor sunt laborum et.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Travel System</title><link>https://ronanchilvers.github.io/posts/a-travel-system/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:52:39 +0100</pubDate><author>ronan@thelittledot.com (Ronan Chilvers)</author><guid>https://ronanchilvers.github.io/posts/a-travel-system/</guid><description>&lt;p>When a journey is undertaken the following steps are followed:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Plan The Route&lt;/strong>
The party selects a route they want to take to their destination, determining how long it will take and what waypoints, if any, they will aim for. If they are at the Kaer, the Guild may be able to help them with maps and historical knowledge of the area.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Prepare To Start&lt;/strong>
The party assigns the journey roles - Guide, Scout, Quartermaster, Wrangler - and gather equipment, rations, etc. They must decide if they are going to use horses or not - if so, the Guild can supply hardy ponies.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Travelling in Role Playing Games</title><link>https://ronanchilvers.github.io/posts/travel-in-rpgs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>ronan@thelittledot.com (Ronan Chilvers)</author><guid>https://ronanchilvers.github.io/posts/travel-in-rpgs/</guid><description>&lt;p>I think it&amp;rsquo;s probably true to say that in most fantasy novels, travel is a crucial part of the story. Characters move through their worlds or into other worlds, undertaking arduous journeys with great risk and meeting various perils and problems along the way.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Frodo and Sam&amp;rsquo;s trek across Middle Earth to Mordor, Waylander&amp;rsquo;s flight from the appalling were-creatures, Rand Al&amp;rsquo;Thor and his friends trekking through many dangers from Emond&amp;rsquo;s Field to the White Tower and beyond. All of these journeys were not only the focus of story - they were the central plot device.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>